<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Posts on The Be Sharps</title><link>https://the-be-sharps.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on The Be Sharps</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 12:23:14 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://the-be-sharps.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Week 4 to 5: Meeting 3</title><link>https://the-be-sharps.github.io/posts/week4-5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 12:23:14 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://the-be-sharps.github.io/posts/week4-5/</guid><description>The first thing we did this meeting was discuss what we did. Máirtín did the comments for the other groups, while Jared and Mark did the discussion board post. Tadhg was unavailable, which is why he is writing the blog post. We reviewed the comments our peers gave to us on our Blackboard post.
Here is the Market Segmentation:
End User Online Gamblers Microtransaction User Online Shopping Application Preventation of spending too much money &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= Benefits Imporve money management &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= Problem addressed Gambling addiction Microtransaction addiction / children spending gamers Shopping addiction Market Characterisitcs 18+ gamers anyone Size of Market International &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= Competition Gamban Microsoft/Sony Banks?</description></item><item><title>Week 3 - Meeting 2</title><link>https://the-be-sharps.github.io/posts/week-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 11:11:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://the-be-sharps.github.io/posts/week-3/</guid><description>Over the course of the weekend, the team discussed a new product idea for this module. We decided upon making an app aimed towards people who use online gambling facilities i.e. Paddy Power, online Bingo etc. We also wanted to accommodate microtransactions included in video games which shared similarities with online betting websites (premium currencies, lootboxes etc). The main goal of this app is to raise the user&amp;rsquo;s awareness of the money being spent and allow them to set a spending cap for a certain time period, slowly weaning them off of these types of gambling.</description></item><item><title>Week 2 - Meeting 1</title><link>https://the-be-sharps.github.io/posts/week-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 17:48:14 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://the-be-sharps.github.io/posts/week-2/</guid><description>The whole team met today following the lecture in the library to try and come up with an idea for a product or service to move forward with next week. We struggled to come up with ideas. Our initial thoughts were to work on something related to COVID-19, but we wanted to create a product or service that would last beyond the pandemic. I mentioned that many industries are moving towards working from home, and that it seems like it will persist beyond the pandemic.</description></item></channel></rss>